# Bryan Burnett

### Software Engineer

#### Contact

(707) 241-3005

bryanburnettbmb@gmail.com

Petaluma, CA

linkedin.com/in/bryan-burnett github.com/crankyhippo bryanburnett.com

### **About Me**

Full Stack developer proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Creating projects using technology is my passion. Over the last decade I've produced, edited, and hosted my own content about all aspects of technology. This has lead me to be a Jack of all trades, and adaptable problem solver. Travel and motorcycle riding is my form of meditation.

#### Education

Full Stack Program | Thinkful March - September 2021

### Skills

- TypeScript

- Express

- HTML / CSS

- REST APIs

- React

- UX / UI

- AWS

- PostgreSQL

- Node.js

- Adobe Creative Suite

- Video Editing

- Graphic Design

### Work Experience

# Production Operator at Google ASG (2021 - Present) Mountain View, CA

- Support for executive level meetings and producing engaging events.
- Internal Subject Matter Expert, training and teaching masterclasses to peers.
- Conceptualize and create custom graphics and design per client needs.

# Operations Tech at Facebook FNTech (2018 - 2021) Menlo Park, CA

- Led client requests and delivered high quality production.
- Built internal Standard Operating Procedures for onboarding new techs and training new technology.
- Created global support site for tracking locations, equipment, and capabilities of numerous FB campus venues.

## Producer at This Week in Tech (TWiT) TWiT (2011 - 2017) Petaluma, CA

- Video editor for daily shows, segments, and product reviews on tight deadlines.
- Managed signal flow and execution of live shows, delegated setup requirements.
- Host of "how-to" show, explaining complex projects ranging from building quad copters to coding projects in a simple digestible manner.

# Projects

### Pomodoro Timer github.com/CrankyHippo/pomodoro-timer

The Pomodoro technique is a time-management method. This was my first project utilizing React.

- Installing packages via NPM.
- Running tests from the command line.
- Writing React function components.